{
  "unitCode": "CITS3403",
  "unitName": "Agile Web Development",
  "testNumber": 1,
  "totalMarks": 14,
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionNumber": null,
      "marks": null,
      "prompt": "",
      "answer": "",
      "questionType": "",
      "totalOptions": ["","","",""]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 1,
      "marks": 1,
      "prompt": "Which tag should surround an entire table of data?",
      "answer": "<table></table>",
      "questionType": "multipleChoice",
      "totalOptions": ["<thead></thead>","<table></table>","<tr></tr>","<td></td>"]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 2,
      "marks": 1,
      "prompt": "Which tag adds new data to a HTML table?",
      "answer": "<td></td>",
      "questionType": "multipleChoice",
      "totalOptions": ["<tb></tb>","<tr></tr>","<td></td>","<table></table>"]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 3,
      "marks": 1,
      "prompt": "Which of the following tags is used to separate the body of a table from its headers and footers?",
      "answer": "<tbody></tbody>",
      "questionType": "multipleChoice",
      "totalOptions": ["<tr></tr>","<thead></thead>","<th></th>","<tbody></tbody>"]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 4,
      "marks": 1,
      "prompt": "Which of the following tags is used to enclose the row of a table containing its headers?",
      "answer": "<thead></thead>",
      "questionType": "multipleChoice",
      "totalOptions": ["<tr></tr>","<thead></thead>","<th></th>","<tbody></tbody>"]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 5,
      "marks": 1,
      "prompt": "Which tag creates new rows in a HTML table?",
      "answer": "<tr></tr>",
      "questionType": "multipleChoice",
      "totalOptions": ["<td></td>","<thead></thead>","<table></table>","<tr></tr>"]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 6,
      "marks": 1,
      "prompt": "Which tag adds a new row header to a HTML table?",
      "answer": "<th scope=\"row\"></th>",
      "questionType": "",
      "totalOptions": ["<tr></tr>","<th></th>","<th scope=\"col\"></th>","<th scope=\"row\"></th>"]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 7,
      "marks": 2,
      "prompt": "What is the name of the tag used to separate the footer of a table from its body?",
      "answer": "tfoot",
      "questionType": "shortAnswer",
      "totalOptions": null
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 8,
      "marks": 2,
      "prompt": "How many columns does the following table row span altogether?\n<tr>\n\t<td colspan=\"2\">Out of Town</td>\n\t<td>Back in Town</td>\n</tr>",
      "answer": "3",
      "questionType": "number",
      "totalOptions": null
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 9,
      "marks": 4,
      "prompt": "The following CSS code adds a 1 px (w) border to (x), and a 1px (y) border to (z). What is w, x, y, and z?\ntd, tr { border: 1px solid black; }\nth { border: 1px solid blue; }",
      "answer": "w: black, x: table rows and cells, y: blue, z: table headers",
      "questionType": "multipleChoice",
      "totalOptions": ["w: black, x: table headers, y: blue, z: table cells",
                       "w: black, x: table rows, y: blue, z: table headers",
                       "w: black, x: table headers, y: blue, z: table rows and cells",
                       "w: black, x: table rows and cells, y: blue, z: table headers"]
    }
  ]
}